Contatta

www.linkedin.com/in/nzopandolfi (LinkedIn) www.nzopandolfi.com/ (Personal)

Competenze principali
HTML 5
CSS3
JavaScript

Languages

Inglese (Professional Working)
Italiano (Native or Bilingual)

Vincenzo Pandolfi

Front-end Developer / iOS Developer Pomigliano d'Arco, Campania, Italia

Riepilogo

I studied Web Design at Ilas Design School and worked in Triboo Digitale and Nascar Web Agency developing responsive multiplatform newsletter, landing pages and E-commerce websites using the most commons front-end libraries and frameworks.

I attended the Apple Developer Academy in Naples, in which I learnt iOS programming and working on projects respecting Agile and Scrum methodologies.

Esperienza

Viniexport
Front-end developer
ottobre 2019 - Present (3 anni 1 mese)
Napoli, Campania, Italia

Front-end developer aprile 2018 - ottobre 2019 (1 anno 7 mesi) Napoli, Italia

Blowhammer Front-end developer dicembre 2017 - marzo 2018 (4 mesi) Nola

Website front-end management and landing pages development for promotional offers.

Apple Developer Academy | Italy iOS Developer gennaio 2017 - settembre 2017 (9 mesi) Napoli, Italia

Triboo Digitale
Email Campaign Developer and Front-end Developer

dicembre 2011 - ottobre 2014 (2 anni 11 mesi)

Email Campaign Developer and Front-end Developer

nascar.it

Email Campaign Developer and Front-end Developer ottobre 2011 - dicembre 2011 (3 mesi)

Email Campaign Developer and Front-end Developer

Formazione

Ilas - Istituto Superiore di Comunicazione Web design, Progettazione pagine web, contenuti digitali/multimediali e risorse informative · (2010 - 2011)

Liceo Scientifico Pedagogico e delle Scienze Sociali "S.Cantone" Indirizzo informatico · (2007)